{
  "version": "1.0",
  "exportDate": "2026-12-18T00:00:00.000Z",
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "Espa√±ol C1",
      "icon": "üá™üá∏",
      "cards": [
        {
          "front": "disminuir",
          "back": "abate"
        },
        {
          "front": "abreviar",
          "back": "abbreviate"
        },
        {
          "front": "abdicar",
          "back": "abdicate"
        },
        {
          "front": "aberraci√≥n",
          "back": "aberration"
        },
        {
          "front": "aborrecer",
          "back": "abhor"
        },
        {
          "front": "cumplir",
          "back": "abide"
        },
        {
          "front": "abundar",
          "back": "abound"
        },
        {
          "front": "resumir",
          "back": "abridge"
        },
        {
          "front": "abrogar",
          "back": "abrogate"
        },
        {
          "front": "abrupto",
          "back": "abrupt"
        },
        {
          "front": "absolver",
          "back": "absolve"
        },
        {
          "front": "abstenerse",
          "back": "abstain"
        },
        {
          "front": "absurdo",
          "back": "absurd"
        },
        {
          "front": "abundancia",
          "back": "abundance"
        },
        {
          "front": "academia",
          "back": "academy"
        },
        {
          "front": "acentuar",
          "back": "accentuate"
        },
        {
          "front": "accesible",
          "back": "accessible"
        },
        {
          "front": "aclamar",
          "back": "acclaim"
        },
        {
          "front": "elogio",
          "back": "accolade"
        },
        {
          "front": "responsable",
          "back": "accountable"
        },
        {
          "front": "acreditaci√≥n",
          "back": "accreditation"
        },
        {
          "front": "acumular",
          "back": "accrue"
        },
        {
          "front": "√°cido",
          "back": "acerbic"
        },
        {
          "front": "reconocer",
          "back": "acknowledge"
        },
        {
          "front": "conocido",
          "back": "acquaintance"
        },
        {
          "front": "consentir",
          "back": "acquiesce"
        },
        {
          "front": "adquisici√≥n",
          "back": "acquisition"
        },
        {
          "front": "absolver",
          "back": "acquit"
        },
        {
          "front": "acre",
          "back": "acrid"
        },
        {
          "front": "acrimonioso",
          "back": "acrimonious"
        },
        {
          "front": "perspicacia",
          "back": "acumen"
        },
        {
          "front": "agudo",
          "back": "acute"
        },
        {
          "front": "inflexible",
          "back": "adamant"
        },
        {
          "front": "ap√©ndice",
          "back": "addendum"
        },
        {
          "front": "experto",
          "back": "adept"
        },
        {
          "front": "adherente",
          "back": "adherent"
        },
        {
          "front": "adyacente",
          "back": "adjacent"
        },
        {
          "front": "adjunto",
          "back": "adjunct"
        },
        {
          "front": "administrador",
          "back": "administrator"
        },
        {
          "front": "admisi√≥n",
          "back": "admittance"
        },
        {
          "front": "amonestar",
          "back": "admonish"
        },
        {
          "front": "adornar",
          "back": "adorn"
        },
        {
          "front": "h√°bil",
          "back": "adroit"
        },
        {
          "front": "adulaci√≥n",
          "back": "adulation"
        },
        {
          "front": "adulterar",
          "back": "adulterate"
        },
        {
          "front": "advenimiento",
          "back": "advent"
        },
        {
          "front": "adversario",
          "back": "adversary"
        },
        {
          "front": "adverso",
          "back": "adverse"
        },
        {
          "front": "adversidad",
          "back": "adversity"
        },
        {
          "front": "defensa",
          "back": "advocacy"
        },
        {
          "front": "est√©tico",
          "back": "aesthetic"
        },
        {
          "front": "afable",
          "back": "affable"
        },
        {
          "front": "afecto",
          "back": "affection"
        },
        {
          "front": "declaraci√≥n jurada",
          "back": "affidavit"
        },
        {
          "front": "afiliar",
          "back": "affiliate"
        },
        {
          "front": "afinidad",
          "back": "affinity"
        },
        {
          "front": "afirmar",
          "back": "affirm"
        },
        {
          "front": "afligir",
          "back": "afflict"
        },
        {
          "front": "pr√≥spero",
          "back": "affluent"
        },
        {
          "front": "secuela",
          "back": "aftermath"
        },
        {
          "front": "agenda",
          "back": "agenda"
        },
        {
          "front": "agravar",
          "back": "aggravate"
        },
        {
          "front": "agregar",
          "back": "aggregate"
        },
        {
          "front": "agresi√≥n",
          "back": "aggression"
        },
        {
          "front": "√°gil",
          "back": "agile"
        },
        {
          "front": "agitar",
          "back": "agitate"
        },
        {
          "front": "agon√≠a",
          "back": "agony"
        },
        {
          "front": "agrario",
          "back": "agrarian"
        },
        {
          "front": "agricultura",
          "back": "agriculture"
        },
        {
          "front": "dolencia",
          "back": "ailment"
        },
        {
          "front": "aunque",
          "back": "albeit"
        },
        {
          "front": "alquimia",
          "back": "alchemy"
        },
        {
          "front": "alienar",
          "back": "alienate"
        },
        {
          "front": "aliviar",
          "back": "alleviate"
        },
        {
          "front": "alianza",
          "back": "alliance"
        },
        {
          "front": "aludir",
          "back": "allude"
        },
        {
          "front": "atractivo",
          "back": "allure"
        },
        {
          "front": "aliado",
          "back": "ally"
        },
        {
          "front": "distante",
          "back": "aloof"
        },
        {
          "front": "alteraci√≥n",
          "back": "alteration"
        },
        {
          "front": "altercado",
          "back": "altercation"
        },
        {
          "front": "altitud",
          "back": "altitude"
        },
        {
          "front": "altruista",
          "back": "altruistic"
        },
        {
          "front": "fusionar",
          "back": "amalgamate"
        },
        {
          "front": "aficionado",
          "back": "amateur"
        },
        {
          "front": "embajador",
          "back": "ambassador"
        },
        {
          "front": "ambiguo",
          "back": "ambiguous"
        },
        {
          "front": "ambivalente",
          "back": "ambivalent"
        },
        {
          "front": "mejorar",
          "back": "ameliorate"
        },
        {
          "front": "dispuesto",
          "back": "amenable"
        },
        {
          "front": "comodidad",
          "back": "amenity"
        },
        {
          "front": "amistoso",
          "back": "amiable"
        },
        {
          "front": "amigable",
          "back": "amicable"
        },
        {
          "front": "munici√≥n",
          "back": "ammunition"
        },
        {
          "front": "amnesia",
          "back": "amnesia"
        },
        {
          "front": "amnist√≠a",
          "back": "amnesty"
        },
        {
          "front": "amorfo",
          "back": "amorphous"
        },
        {
          "front": "amplificar",
          "back": "amplify"
        },
        {
          "front": "an√°logo",
          "back": "analogous"
        },
        {
          "front": "analog√≠a",
          "back": "analogy"
        },
        {
          "front": "anarquista",
          "back": "anarchist"
        },
        {
          "front": "anarqu√≠a",
          "back": "anarchy"
        },
        {
          "front": "anatom√≠a",
          "back": "anatomy"
        },
        {
          "front": "ascendencia",
          "back": "ancestry"
        },
        {
          "front": "an√©cdota",
          "back": "anecdote"
        },
        {
          "front": "animar",
          "back": "animate"
        },
        {
          "front": "animosidad",
          "back": "animosity"
        },
        {
          "front": "anexar",
          "back": "annex"
        },
        {
          "front": "aniquilar",
          "back": "annihilate"
        },
        {
          "front": "anotar",
          "back": "annotate"
        },
        {
          "front": "anular",
          "back": "annul"
        },
        {
          "front": "anomal√≠a",
          "back": "anomaly"
        },
        {
          "front": "an√≥nimo",
          "back": "anonymous"
        },
        {
          "front": "antagonista",
          "back": "antagonist"
        },
        {
          "front": "antagonizar",
          "back": "antagonize"
        },
        {
          "front": "antecedente",
          "back": "antecedent"
        },
        {
          "front": "antolog√≠a",
          "back": "anthology"
        },
        {
          "front": "antropolog√≠a",
          "back": "anthropology"
        },
        {
          "front": "ant√≠doto",
          "back": "antidote"
        },
        {
          "front": "anticuado",
          "back": "antiquated"
        },
        {
          "front": "antiguo",
          "back": "antique"
        },
        {
          "front": "antis√©ptico",
          "back": "antiseptic"
        },
        {
          "front": "ant√≠tesis",
          "back": "antithesis"
        },
        {
          "front": "apat√≠a",
          "back": "apathy"
        },
        {
          "front": "√°pice",
          "back": "apex"
        },
        {
          "front": "apocalipsis",
          "back": "apocalypse"
        },
        {
          "front": "apolog√©tico",
          "back": "apologetic"
        },
        {
          "front": "disculpa",
          "back": "apology"
        },
        {
          "front": "ap√≥stol",
          "back": "apostle"
        },
        {
          "front": "horrorizar",
          "back": "appall"
        },
        {
          "front": "aparato",
          "back": "apparatus"
        },
        {
          "front": "vestimenta",
          "back": "apparel"
        },
        {
          "front": "ap√©ndice",
          "back": "appendix"
        },
        {
          "front": "aplicable",
          "back": "applicable"
        },
        {
          "front": "solicitante",
          "back": "applicant"
        },
        {
          "front": "aplicaci√≥n",
          "back": "application"
        },
        {
          "front": "evaluaci√≥n",
          "back": "appraisal"
        },
        {
          "front": "apreciar",
          "back": "appreciate"
        },
        {
          "front": "aprehender",
          "back": "apprehend"
        },
        {
          "front": "aprensivo",
          "back": "apprehensive"
        },
        {
          "front": "aprendiz",
          "back": "apprentice"
        },
        {
          "front": "apropiado",
          "back": "appropriate"
        },
        {
          "front": "aproximado",
          "back": "approximate"
        },
        {
          "front": "aptitud",
          "back": "aptitude"
        },
        {
          "front": "arbitrario",
          "back": "arbitrary"
        },
        {
          "front": "arbitrar",
          "back": "arbitrate"
        },
        {
          "front": "arcada",
          "back": "arcade"
        },
        {
          "front": "arqueolog√≠a",
          "back": "archaeology"
        },
        {
          "front": "arcaico",
          "back": "archaic"
        },
        {
          "front": "arzobispo",
          "back": "archbishop"
        },
        {
          "front": "arquitecto",
          "back": "architect"
        },
        {
          "front": "archivo",
          "back": "archive"
        },
        {
          "front": "ardiente",
          "back": "ardent"
        },
        {
          "front": "arduo",
          "back": "arduous"
        },
        {
          "front": "aristocracia",
          "back": "aristocracy"
        },
        {
          "front": "arist√≥crata",
          "back": "aristocrat"
        },
        {
          "front": "aritm√©tica",
          "back": "arithmetic"
        },
        {
          "front": "armamento",
          "back": "armament"
        },
        {
          "front": "armisticio",
          "back": "armistice"
        },
        {
          "front": "armadura",
          "back": "armour"
        },
        {
          "front": "arom√°tico",
          "back": "aromatic"
        },
        {
          "front": "acusar",
          "back": "arraign"
        },
        {
          "front": "arrogante",
          "back": "arrogant"
        },
        {
          "front": "arsenal",
          "back": "arsenal"
        },
        {
          "front": "incendio provocado",
          "back": "arson"
        },
        {
          "front": "arterial",
          "back": "arterial"
        },
        {
          "front": "arteria",
          "back": "artery"
        },
        {
          "front": "articular",
          "back": "articulate"
        },
        {
          "front": "artificio",
          "back": "artifice"
        },
        {
          "front": "artesano",
          "back": "artisan"
        },
        {
          "front": "averiguar",
          "back": "ascertain"
        },
        {
          "front": "asc√©tico",
          "back": "ascetic"
        },
        {
          "front": "atribuir",
          "back": "ascribe"
        },
        {
          "front": "as√©ptico",
          "back": "aseptic"
        },
        {
          "front": "avergonzado",
          "back": "ashamed"
        },
        {
          "front": "ceniciento",
          "back": "ashen"
        },
        {
          "front": "en tierra",
          "back": "ashore"
        },
        {
          "front": "aparte",
          "back": "aside"
        },
        {
          "front": "torcido",
          "back": "askew"
        },
        {
          "front": "dormido",
          "back": "asleep"
        },
        {
          "front": "aspiraci√≥n",
          "back": "aspiration"
        },
        {
          "front": "asaltar",
          "back": "assail"
        },
        {
          "front": "asesino",
          "back": "assassin"
        },
        {
          "front": "asesinar",
          "back": "assassinate"
        },
        {
          "front": "ensayar",
          "back": "assay"
        },
        {
          "front": "conjunto",
          "back": "assemblage"
        },
        {
          "front": "asamblea",
          "back": "assembly"
        },
        {
          "front": "asentir",
          "back": "assent"
        },
        {
          "front": "afirmaci√≥n",
          "back": "assertion"
        },
        {
          "front": "evaluaci√≥n",
          "back": "assessment"
        },
        {
          "front": "asiduo",
          "back": "assiduous"
        },
        {
          "front": "asignaci√≥n",
          "back": "assignment"
        },
        {
          "front": "asimilar",
          "back": "assimilate"
        },
        {
          "front": "asistencia",
          "back": "assistance"
        },
        {
          "front": "asistente",
          "back": "assistant"
        },
        {
          "front": "asociaci√≥n",
          "back": "association"
        },
        {
          "front": "surtido",
          "back": "assorted"
        },
        {
          "front": "surtido",
          "back": "assortment"
        },
        {
          "front": "aplacar",
          "back": "assuage"
        },
        {
          "front": "suposici√≥n",
          "back": "assumption"
        },
        {
          "front": "garant√≠a",
          "back": "assurance"
        },
        {
          "front": "asteroide",
          "back": "asteroid"
        },
        {
          "front": "asma",
          "back": "asthma"
        },
        {
          "front": "asombrar",
          "back": "astound"
        },
        {
          "front": "extraviado",
          "back": "astray"
        },
        {
          "front": "a horcajadas",
          "back": "astride"
        },
        {
          "front": "astrolog√≠a",
          "back": "astrology"
        },
        {
          "front": "astronauta",
          "back": "astronaut"
        },
        {
          "front": "astronom√≠a",
          "back": "astronomy"
        },
        {
          "front": "astuto",
          "back": "astute"
        },
        {
          "front": "asilo",
          "back": "asylum"
        },
        {
          "front": "asimetr√≠a",
          "back": "asymmetry"
        },
        {
          "front": "ateo",
          "back": "atheist"
        },
        {
          "front": "atleta",
          "back": "athlete"
        },
        {
          "front": "atl√©tico",
          "back": "athletic"
        },
        {
          "front": "atlas",
          "back": "atlas"
        },
        {
          "front": "atmosf√©rico",
          "back": "atmospheric"
        },
        {
          "front": "√°tomo",
          "back": "atom"
        },
        {
          "front": "at√≥mico",
          "back": "atomic"
        },
        {
          "front": "expiar",
          "back": "atone"
        },
        {
          "front": "atroz",
          "back": "atrocious"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}